sup everyone Tamers12345 1 2 3 4 5 feet with
a very special video today so today's
gonna be kind of different usually
instead of like making my own thing I
thought hey you know be cool if I go
looking at some old sock undergone
websites and some [ __ ] and I beginning a
lava quest for this for this website
called Manic Panic
or some [ __ ] softly yeah I go I can do
that
apparently this was a very old website
for Mac 2007 in 2006 I think at least I
think that's what it said yeah - 2006
yeah God I love that cool man a human at
the bottom that's pretty badass if you
ask me I also love these to cut out and
pasted it crapoly pasted mannix with the
green glow that's it's pretty badass I
could do it better but that's not will
here talk about we have just have fun
and just look when around the website
yes so let's see for the updates it
stopped in 2010 if you're looking at
this thank you for checking back yeah
okay oh I haven't been able to look on
this website even if I walked it - as
you can see it was so basic that person
say yeah [ __ ] you [ __ ] I don't want
to anymore
Tisa so let's get started
feature oh we got a lot to look at this
do you love Manic but we're gonna find
out oh oh
do you love 9 do you belong here Manic
Panic let's find out oh oh [ __ ]
you know you love Manic if you're
surprised I found my home wasn't
nominated for grounding you insist that
vest in green hairspray all the latest
would in fact yeah maybe 2006 you are
undergoing therapy
for kleptomania what the [ __ ] your
favorite nuts like I said a song out
it's not easy being and Manic Monday
Manic is just his name what the [ __ ]
okay then it's working fine good [ __ ]
you're you're leave the house with L
pants for never without your trusty job
six that's pretty [ __ ] up sub an
ordinate number of people Reger ask if
you are stoned so basically you you love
Manic if you're a thief who doesn't wear
pants who does rugs Oh with green hair
toe who listens to it's not easy being
green in Manic Monday
you refuse to admit that big tecna's
went out in the 70s [ __ ] this is 2016
oh oh she I can go back oh damn golly we
go [ __ ] okay so I guess I don't love
Manic okay then oh [ __ ] whoops I just
[ __ ] phrase [ __ ] [ __ ] guess I'm
going back to Manic fashion whatever
that it okay I guess I'll just do this
what do I do
I'm stuck what is it how do I get to
Manic fashion I press back how did it
take me here okay I guess we'll look at
Manic fashion
are you Manic about Matt what what does
matic mean do you go spicy dressed like
our favorite green Hedgehog well I will
pants oh this is a must for Manic fans
these can be find any goth retail store
like Hot Topic that they are gold
earrings are burst a fanny pack in Wagga
so basically it's saying don't wear
pants is is that what these weapons
trying to say don't wear pants yeah
welcome back [ __ ] had to reload the
page guess we'll click on points to
ponder next but I love this website
[ __ ] oh my God okay sibling favoritism
retake on favoritism places abandoned so
basically is this website all about
saying mannix in like all along was it
oh the Max favor foot Manic is seen
getting apples from the market Stan he
gets a green apple so this means I'm AG
fair food could be apples okay then
I mean he's seen eating chili dogs too
he see he seen stealing a packet of
mustard and ketchup it is most of these
fair food damn my head talks birthday I
cannot know what the Hedgehog's birthday
is I'm not stupid
gave the Hedgehogs the Hedgehogs birth
order is gonna be wrong I know it is
because I know it is the three of
separating the birthday on the same day
but this seems playing calling them
started to be our triplets yeah we know
this [ __ ] they say them the [ __ ] how
the triplets are born to thrown away
hates Sonic is the awkward but the fun
and [ __ ] I'm still seeing after
fourteen awesome eh pants a sock all
this song of Miller Mac is the baby that
is not true Sonia is the oldest Sonic is
then the mill child the Nanak is the
youngest so they got Manic rapper yeah I
guess it's not smile know this [ __ ] I
know this [ __ ]
I gotta say this Manic is not
left-handed they say he is right-handed
they actually say that in one of the
episodes that is not true either okay so
I'm just going into that stupid [ __ ] now
guess what we'll go to man now getting
creative Manic movie why don't we see
what that is [ __ ] Oh are we going
Devin up in this [ __ ] come on speed it
up Manic movie project so basically this
is a Manic movie that never went through
and got canceled
where's being made by random people no
Bobby no Bobby Bobby's not in the movie
I don't want to watch the movie so who
Manek man is worse make wise man if man
was Nana who saw it who slayed Inga
who's mama they need a voice for swamp
it's a robot just get the [ __ ] wall I
know I don't wanna watch this movie this
movie is [ __ ] this movie is yeah guess
we're going back to Manic Panic [ __ ]
Manic out ok going back to creative all
of this is gonna be good
we're looking to Manic out girl I mean
why the [ __ ] not
I mean this is gonna be good car crappy
fan I from only 2000 some [ __ ] God seeks
so long to load oh [ __ ]
Mac computer I do a mini picture Mac
same with drumsticks no back when I'm so
lazy
damn so hours draw him very well with
the masses you see how
to do and out of has because let's do
the detail of the her no we did it come
on I wanna see this Eclipse one this
woman looks so good oh [ __ ] that is
terrified what is that what is this I
decided to go with the overdramatic look
with the triplet style so is that the is
that the styles in the opening it it's a
it says it's a gift
does it yet the balm it says glitz
glimpse of destiny dog give so we're
gonna see this [ __ ] okay so it's not a
gift or at least it was saved as a gift
but it's not where this is 2006 I'm sure
people don't not to use a computer we'll
go to Manic fanfiction [ __ ] this is
nothing good about me
I mean of no fat fake Osaka and is it
tends to be good when I don't make it
Sonic on the ground next Jam this series
if it will be one is set 16 years after
the fall of a box Empire at the hands of
the castle for 16 [ __ ] years all this
one looks good Mannix Mannix xscape a
brief look at what the future holds for
Manic drama PG all this one down here
looks good so we'll save this for I
asked some fans really go the extra mile
what comes to Manic enthusiasm when they
can't find a Mac eye socket to fill the
desires they take mouse to their own
hands this page was Chris specially for
my few other things you'd like to share
please send it to fan submissions and
Manic Panic
see Manic animation number one I thought
this was fan creations not just posting
gifts of the show how they all work
there I gotta see this [ __ ] no you can
do that how this is a meticulous if you
own hands just watch the [ __ ] child
yeah it's just oh that's from the Bob
yup so yeah that's Bobby's house by the
way I'm just sayin saying up in this
[ __ ] wink yeah so I come and I remember
that too that's one what's the [ __ ]
song [ __ ] never easy [ __ ] that's it
never easy
that's one Sonia sayings we're good to
Marik's holiday adventure game oh we got
video games look at this [ __ ] is that
game all this is gonna oh this is taking
an ass into your own hands I Louie on
you but take note from festive blacks
let's play this [ __ ]
Mannix holiday game just like Christmas
I believe this [ __ ] this will take
about two to three minutes don't on a
dial-up connection so what's a dial-up
connection this is 2016 I don't know
what the [ __ ] that is so you may want to
read this positively spellbinding
expansion of the game in the meantime I
also want to play the game how do I play
the game
do I do I need a dog like what's
dialogue collection oh no it's a job
connection
what's a dialogue connection I want to I
just wanna play a game God there's like
Matt it's all I see you down here
so like Max help or something okay I was
right gets this Christmas is here the
candy cane
maybe I gotta look this duck like a
Manic Panic I just want to play the game
so you cannot I'll play the game cuz I
don't have a job nation
maybe I got wait wait something's Lola
is it loli
is it dead alright so do I need to die
up I gotta see what that connection is a
dial-up connection internet access is a
form of internet access that uses the
facilities of the public switch
telephone network PSTN to establish
connection to internet server provider
ISP by dealing a telephone number or
convento telephone line
what's a telephone line well what do I
do I need you have what what so I need a
wire hooked to my phone can you do that
okay so I guess I'm not playing a game
Mac's holiday my ass I guess there's
only one thing left
Manek stuffed doll let's click on that
that this really kept my first boom oh
no somebody actually took a picture of
yourself
it is now stuck here forever please tell
me this is fake this is a joke this is a
joke
a hole
this is a joke I don't know
oh no oh no no no no please no oh no no
oh [ __ ]
there's two of that oh oh no that's not
maybe that's like a green ring that's a
great vein oh [ __ ] oh my God Oh No
taking matters into your own hands they
weren't joking just we'll go to the best
of Manic or SU personality I don't know
nothing will beat that uh-uh
I feel bad for this [ __ ] I mean habits
of a heavy effective Manic fan okay so
this is habits of Manic okay babe oh
this is gonna be good
you carry your drumsticks around with
you all the time you use it for the out
of self-defense by knocking on anyone's
head comes near you oh my God you often
try to hover on your hoverboard but you
always end up in the hospital I have
every attempt you drop your head dial-up
green like a brush you know that's
probably true